export const Grambasic=[
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a noun?",
    Options: ["Book", "Sing", "Angry", "Love"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a noun?",
    Options: ["Given", "To", "Travel", "John"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not a noun?",
    Options: ["Park", "Bus", "Long", "All of these"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a plural noun?",
    Options: ["People", "Tiger", "Bee", "Donkey"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a proper noun?",
    Options: ["Animal", "Obama", "Needle", "Hammer"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Haris is a poor man. In this sentence, the word 'man' is:",
    Options: ["Common Noun", "Proper Noun", "Collective Noun", "Abstract Noun"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "A noun is the name of some particular person, place, or thing.",
    Options: ["Proper", "Common", "Abstract", "Countable"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following noun is an abstract noun?",
    Options: ["Slavery", "Girl", "Horse", "Doctor"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Pick out uncountable noun from the following.",
    Options: ["Sister", "Boy", "Slave", "Oil"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "The police the crowd) The 'crowed' is noun.",
    Options: ["Proper", "Abstract", "Collective", "Countable"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  }
]
